I'm an introvert and I have spent a
large portion of my life enjoying my own
inner world in my head or in a world the
outer world experiencing other people's
worlds through books and movies and
other way you enjoyed those things and I
enjoy creating those worlds
I don't enjoy the other part of writing
and creating the characterization in the
story but I do enjoy creating worlds and
new rules and now that I'm in my
mid-thirties its falling away it doesn't
have the same draw that it used to but
it's also been replaced by a world a
different world in my head that is
possible it's not based on time travel
or aliens coming or futuristic
technology that doesn't exist or magic
it there's no piece of it that isn't
achievable now and so now my mission is
to and I'm an introvert yeah I don't
want to be doing a YouTube channel I
don't want to be being a business owner
and a project manager and a leader I
will be if I need to be right now but
I'm going to create a system so that
other introverts don't have to do this
but I need right now I biggest struggle
is that I don't know how to do this I
don't know how to express this world
that I know as possible and solves the
vast majority of our problems
in a way that people get it where they
aren't able to see it like I do to feel
it like I do I can explain in little
bits the house I'd the logical here's
what we do but not here's why we do it
yeah but I was just writing about that
this feeling of being exactly who I'm
supposed to be and not which is an
ongoing theme for me especially at the
moment needing to be not need to be
anything just accepting exactly who I am
my abilities my limitations my desires
my propulsions like just acknowledging
that these things exist and accepting
them and realizing how much of Who I am
the dark side the light side the
horrible things the amazing things have
happened had led me to this point and
it's a fun journey to discover for all
those little things along the way like
when you get to the end of a book and
then you reread it and you see all the
little the little pieces that led you up
there that's life and seen the little
pieces that lead you up there when you
go back over it it's cool I've enjoyed
it but that's the inner work that I need
to do the world needs this outer work
and I don't know how to do the inner
work fast enough to be the person I need
to be in this one area because I can
accept myself in every other way but I
can't accept that I'm not able to be to
get this out there too
that I'm not
I spent a lot of my time not knowing how
to do this the interior world solid
there the solution that it's a solution
how we get there how we have a peaceful
revolution from where we are to where we
need to be we're not going to annihilate
our species I have the solution and it's
in my head
and I don't know how to communicate it
to the world